[
    {
        "front": "えきいん",
        "back": "station employee",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "わすれもの",
        "back": "forgotten item",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "たしか",
        "back": "reliable; definitely",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃりょう",
        "back": "car",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "ペットボトル",
        "back": "PET bottle",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "かくにん（する）",
        "back": "to check",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "れんらく（する）",
        "back": "to let (someone) know; to contact",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひつような",
        "back": "needed",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょるい",
        "back": "documents",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "とどける",
        "back": "to bring; to deliver",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）とどく",
        "back": "to arrive",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうに",
        "back": "suddenly",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "むかう",
        "back": "to leave (for); to head",
        "chapter": "N4 C23"
    }
]